imtranslator.net 2017-12-31

# Privacy of Smart Link Corporation.

| 

**Privacy Policy**

Smart Link Corporation is committed to respecting and protecting your personal privacy. Our privacy policy is succinctly explained below.  
Questions regarding our privacy policy should be directed to: 

**Smart Link Corporation  
Phone: (949) 552 1599   
Fax: (949) 552 1699   
Contact form **

**Collected Information**  
Whenever you visit our online services, Smart Link Corporation's web servers automatically collect and aggregate information from your web browser including your IP address, browser type, operating system, pages you access, date and time of your visit, Smart Link web sites cookie information and time spent on each web page. 

**Use of Information**  
Smart Link Corporation uses this anonymous information to customize your experience on our site, to show you more relevant advertising messages, and to improve our services in general. For example, when you use online Translator, Smart Link can collect aggregate information such as the language pairs used and number of translations done on each language pair to provide more relevant advertisements. We do not attempt to link this information to a specific person.

**Logging IP Addresses**  
For each visitor to our web page, our web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or email address. 

**Collecting Email Addresses**  
We will only use this information to administer our mailings to you. Smart Link Corporation does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with third parties.

**Certain Exceptional Disclosures**  
Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal processes.

**Text Processing Security**  
We use appropriate security measures to protect information that you provide to us for translation purposes. We only store the provided text during system operations such as Decoding, Spell Checking, Dictionary queries, Back Translation and Translation. We purge our systems of your text and no logs or cookies are kept after you leave our web sites. 

**Use of Cookies**  
No personal information is stored in the cookie.

**Security Measures**  
We operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your user data.

**Third-Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**Third-Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

The third-party advertisers may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as to stop you seeing the same ad over and over again, to detect and stop click fraud, and to show ads that are likely to be more relevant (such as ads based on websites you have visited). 

**Acceptance of terms**  
By using our services, accessing our website or purchasing our products you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use described in this policy 

This privacy policy applies to web pages ending in [paralink.com](http://www.paralink.com/), [imtranslator.com](http://www.imtranslator.com/) or [imtranslator.net](http://www.imtranslator.net/) that contain a link to this privacy policy at the bottom of the web page. 

If you have any questions about this, contact us at [privacy-support](http://imtranslator.net/contacts.asp).

|
